

Applicant for:

Android Developer (Java/Kotlin) ~ 2000\$

Dr.JOY 22 April 2020

Nguyen Thanh Duy

★ thanhduy1665@gmail.com

What skills, work projects or achievements make you a strong candidate for this position?

Note from ITviec: Nguyen Thanh Duy skipped the cover letter.

Nguyen Thanh Duy

0762375160 thanhduy1665@gmail.com

__

Summary

Experienced Full Stack Engineer with a history of working on large traffic applications. I can handle the entire software development life cycle. As an experienced trainer, I can share my knowledge and experience with others to help the team for growth. I'm interested in large-scale systems and want to make a career based on it (Realtime processing, BigData, etc.).

Experience

ZALO OFFICIAL ACCOUNT (ZALO PAGE) / Fullstack developer

JUNE 2017 - PRESENT

- Platform is similar to Facebook Fan Page.
- Responsibilities:
- + Build back-end, middle-ware for the system with my team.
- + Build system manage fan page for publishers.
- + Build operator tool.
- Technologies used : Java , Memcached , Redis , Mysql , NoSql , Javascript , Angularjs , Elasticsearch , Micro service with Thrift protocol ...

Ziggedy company / Senior PHP developer

JULY 2015 - MAY 2017

- Development tools: Eclipse, sublime, mysgl workbench, Git
- Technology used: Yii Framework,, Apache Solr, Spring, AngularJS, Ajax, CSS, HTML, XML, Javascript, Mysql

The work done: database and business logic on website.

1/ Affiliated network

- Amazon api, popshop, cj network
- Programming job (console app) runs background to call api from third party ,get xml data (parse xml) from the affiliated network after that insert them (deal) into the database.
- 2/ Single page: Task already did: Apply AngularJs to build single page show all information about user

3/ connection between java and php

- Using activemq as message transportation to talk between PHP and Java
- Task already did: when user sends mail, code PHP will send message to activemq (using storm library to talk with activemq) and after that Java will read message from activemq and after that Java will use Mandrill or Mailchimp service mail to send mail.

4/ Search using apache solr

- Using apache Solr to index some columns in Mysql when we are searching using data return form Solr (only array id) and after that using id to query data from mysql
- Task already did: search deal and product on website
- 5/ Coding mobile api for application call: Coding restful api functions as login, signup, forgot password for app call

Ziggedy company / PHP developer

AUGUST 2013 - JUNE 2015

- The work done: design interface and database Development tools: Netbeans, Mysql workbench
- Technology used: PHP, Ajax, CSS, HTML, XML, Javascript, Mysql

FPT company / Java Developer

MARCH 2012 - JULY 2013

- The work done: design interface and database
- Development tools: Eclipse
- Technology used: Java, HTML, XML, Mysql

Education

HO CHI MINH UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE / Bachelor Degree in Software

Engineering

2008 - 2012

HO CHI MINH UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE / Study Masters in Computer Science.

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

- Java programming experience with Java Core, J2EE, Java Web, Spring framework, Rest API Service.
- Web programming experience (Javascript, Angular JS, Vuejs is the best).
- Database experience with Mysql, Sql Server, Nosql as MongoDb
- Caching system experience with Memcache, Redis ...
- Strong scale system with micro service used Thrift Apache or Protobuf.
- Knowledge Golang, NodeJs, ReactJs, VueJs, Docker, Elasticsearch, Big Data.
- Knowledge of Object-Oriented Programming.
- Algorithms Analysis and Design.
- Platform : Linux, Windows, MacOs
- Source code management : GIT, SVN.

SOFT SKILLS

- Work independently or teamwork.
- I have experience managing teams of more than 5 members.
- Thinking and resolving problems quickly.
- Learn new experiences and knowledge via the Internet and colleagues around.
- Friendly and sociable people.

Skills